Guide to the John Gerassi Oral History Collection ALBA.AUDIO.018
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Oral History Interviews
  - Tisa, John and May, 1980; cuid244 (Box 2, Cd ALBA A 18-199, Box 8, Audiocassette 18_199)
  - Watt, George, 1980; cuid9240 (Box 8, Audiocassette 18_200)
  - Watt, George, 1980; cuid9241 (Box 2, Cd ALBA A 18-201 A-B, Box 8, Audiocassette 18_201)
  - Watt, George, 1980; cuid9242 (Box 1, Cd ALBA A 18-202 A-B, Box 8, Audiocassette 18_202)
  - Watt, George, 1980; cuid9243 (Box 2, Cd ALBA A 18-203 A-B, Box 8, Audiocassette 18_203)
  - Watt, George, 1980; cuid9244 (Box 2, Cd ALBA A 18-204 A-B, Box 8, Audiocassette 18_204)
  - Waywood, Wally, 1980; cuid9245 (Box 2, Cd ALBA A 18-205 A-B, Box 9, Audiocassette 18_205)
  - Weissman, Irving, 1980; cuid9246 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_206)
  - Weissman, Irving, 1980; cuid9247 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_207)
  - Weissman, Irving, 1980; cuid9248 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_208)
  - Weissman, Irving, 1980; cuid9249 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_209)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9250 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_210)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9251 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_211)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9252 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_212)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9253 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_213)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9254 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_214)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9255 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_215)
  - Wellman, Saul, 1980; cuid9256 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_216)
  - Wolff, Milton, 1980; cuid9257 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_217)
  - Wolff, Milton, 1980; cuid9258 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_218)
  - Wolff, Milton, 1980; cuid9259 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_219)
  - Wolff, Milton, 1980; cuid9260 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_220)
  - Wolff, Milton, 1980; cuid9261 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_221)
  - Wolff, Milton, 1980; cuid9262 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_222)
  - Zawadowski, Joe, 1980; cuid9263 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_223)
  - Veterans' Anniversary Event: African American Veterans Honored., Undated; cuid9264 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_224)
  - Veterans' Research Notes: Cleveland University, Undated; cuid9265 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_225)
  - Veterans'Research Notes: Toronto Public Library, Undated; cuid9266 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_226)
  - Villis, Ray: Contract with Gerassi, Undated; cuid9267 (Box 9, Audiocassette 18_227)